I'm going to say where that comes from clearly
voy a decir de dónde sale eso claramente
apart from the mouths of several YouTubers and
aparte de por boca de varios youtuber y
people who were there, I don't know if they would see it, maybe I'm
gente que estuvo por allí no sé si vería
flirting, I want to talk to them and they
a lo mejor tonteo se los quiero hablar y
interpreted it badly, I don't know, okay, what I
lo interpretaron viejo mal no lo sé vale
can say is that this is from 2018,
lo que sí puedo decir que eso es de 2018
which was already talked about in its day, that there were
que ya se habló en su día que hubo
Salcedo channels that already talked about it and
canales de salcedo que ya lo hablaron y
that today they have the videos
que hoy en día tienen los vídeos
deleted, for example, gossip YouTuber or he
borrados por ejemplo chisme youtuber o
doesn't have it deleted immediately but he
no lo tiene borrados inmediato pero lo
has it since supposedly in the element
tiene ya que supuestamente en elemento
of blonds in the form where the
de rubios de forma donde se hizo el
tournament was held in Spain, supposedly he says mex
torneo en españa supuestamente dice mex
and vergas that a source gave him
y que una fuente le pasó
information that there are gameplays and
información de que hay gameplays y
free also had some
libres también tenido unas relaciones
sexual relations that doesn't take him a month and a dick for
carnales eso no le lleva mes y por
an email, look at the one he had in the frozen
un email mira la que tuvo en el helada
Mary was a friend of Wind and her
mary fue una amiga de wind y que se
name is Dan, so surely Daniel
llama dan ya entonces seguramente daniel
told Wind and so Wind made her send
le dijo a wind y para que wind hice la
Meseberg to which Messi Vereda is
mandara meseberg a que messi vereda es
like the spokesperson for the people who don't
como como el vocero de la gente que no
want to get their hands dirty
se quiere manchar la manita
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah